It works!
Cold weather's not going to stop Vick!
Briar, I'm literally starving here!
Where are those fish you promised me?
Under the snow and ice, I bet!
Hey, Briar!
Briar?
I found our fishing spot.
Hey, Bramble, find a way to break the ice
so we can get the fish.
You sure fish are down there?
That's right. Right here. Now get going, okay?
Yeah!
Come on, fish!
Great, keep going at it. The fish are right underneath you.
Hey, Bramble!
That was scary!
I don't even know how to swim!
Ah! Great!
Oh boy!
They look delicious!
I gotta have one!
Alright, job well done!
Now it's time to chow down.
Oh, I got one! I got one!
Hey, come back!
I gotcha!
Gotcha!
You did it! We got it, brother!
Hey, get back here. That's just great.
Vick!
Oh my log!
Oh my head hurts.
Briar, did you catch the fish?
It's Logger Vick.
Why is it always those two dumb bears?
Hey, Vicky, you just cost me a fish.
Now you're gonna get it.
Oh, did I?
You owe us.
Right, go on.
Show them what you're made of.
Bring it on, Fluffer Teddy Bears.
What? Bramble.
Hard
Let's see you try and do that again, Mr. Vick.
Is that all you've got, then? Bring it on.
Time for double speed.
Oh, yeah.
Is this all I got left?
Bramble, let's go.
OK.
Oh, yeah.
Close, but no cigar.
Come back here.
You can't get us.
I'm gonna bag you two!
You look just like Elmer Fudd!
Where's my hat?
Where's my hat at?
Stop mocking me!
Looks like the little Vicky doesn't know how to skate.
I'll show you! I'm a natural!
Look at him, Bramble. He can't even stand up straight on the ice.
You! Two stinking bears!
Real quick.
Now check this out.
Oh, OK.
Right.
I'm...
Gotta get you guys!
What are you guys doing?
Hey, Vicky, can I borrow that hat for a second?
Hey, give me back my hat!
Hey, I'm Vicky!
Bramble, check this.
Got it!
Whoa!
Here I go!
That was a close one.
Oh, man.
Ah. You want this? Come and get it.
Uh. Ah! I hate you, bears.
Huh? What's that? I got an idea.
Hey, Vicky, why don't you come get it?
Let me try.
I'm ugly Logger Vick.
Now that I've got some new kicks,
I'm gonna give you bears the boot.
Now, you two bears, go ahead and laugh.
Once I get my hands on you two,
I'm gonna turn you into bear patties.
Come and get me, Vicky!
Come back here.
Stop skating away.
Oh, I'm terrified.
Come and get me.
I wonder what's better. Dark or light meat.
Hey, Bramble.
Give it back, you dumb tree!
Let's hope he never pulls it out.
Now.
A Tutu?
What are those bears doing now?
Look, quit being a pest!
So you both think you're figure skaters now, huh?
Hey, Bramble, come on, hurry up!
He can't catch me!
Neener, neener!
Okay, time to see what this baby can do!
I'm gonna get you two!
Quick, let's go.
Is he okay?
Alright, step back, I'm trained in CPR.
A fish?
He's like a fish dispenser.
Oh wow, Briar! That's great!
Let's use him to catch fish every time!